

### **Contacts**

Russia, Moscow

- yurakholoimov@ya.ru
- +7(977)264-1610
- @yuriykholoimov
- in/yuriykholoimov
- vk.com/holoim
- /YuraKholoimov
  - codewars.com/users/YuraKholoimov

### **Employers feadback**

Bacalim Sergey tech.lead, company "OPERA" email: info@upgradefor.com

# **Yuriy Kholoimov**

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### About me

Front-End developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, Typescript, HTML, CSS, JS. I'm always looking forward to improve my expertise. I'm planing to study Node.js, because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. Usually I like spend my leisure time on Codewars.

### Skills

- REACT / REDUX
- JS / TYPESCRIPT
- TDD / JEST / STORYBOOK
- AXIOS / REST API
- Formik / Redux-form
- HTML & CSS / SCSS
- GIT / GITHUB
- BEM / BOOTSTRAP / MUI

## Work experience

### MOBIRISE.COM

Front-end developer Website Builder Company mobirise.com/ru/ November 2021 - H. B.

- Development of widgets, modules for various types of website-builder templates on React TypeScript.
- Optimization of the best solution for rendering JSX elements.
- Fixing applications issues & unit testing.

### **FREELANCE**

Front-end developer | February 2021 - May 2021

- Developed portfolio-site, lendings for customers.
- Created complex forms, with sorting and searching.
- Optimized React App using native and architectural methods.
- Fixing applications issues.
- Ensuring security and providing services on board the aircraft.

### **AEROFLOT**

Senier cabine crew | October 2015 - Sep.2021

### **Education**

### **RUSSIAN ACADEMY NE&CS**

October 2021

### RUSSIAN ACADEMY NE&CS

Bachelor of Science September 2005 - March 2009

### **OREL STATE TECHNICAL** UNIVERSITY

September 2002 - May 2005

Applied Informatics in Economics. Moscow.

Management of state and municipal government.

Orel.

Management of state and municipal government.

Secondary vocational education in Livny.

### Courses

#### **IT-INCUBATOR**

2022

#### **UDEMY**

2021

### HTML ACADEMY

2020

#### Front-end developer (React/TS)

The Complete JavaScript Course 2021, by Jonas Schmedtmann

JavaScript for begginers, HTML and CSS for begginers